-And now the Kung Pao Chicken.
-Yeah, smooth. Ha, ha.
And finally, my Moo Shu Pork.
LEONARD:
Whoo-hoo!
There you have it, gentlemen.
Our entire dinner unpacked by robot.
And it only took 28 minutes.
-Impressive, but we must be cautious.
-Why?
Today,
it's a Chinese-food-retrieval robot.
Tomorrow, it travels back in time
and tries to kill Sarah Connor.
I don't think that's gonna happen,
Sheldon.
No one ever does.
That's why it happens.
Hey. Is the food here?
Ooh, what's that?
That, dear lady,
is the Wolowitz Programmable Hand...
...designed for extravehicular repairs
on the International Space Station.
-Oh, cool.
-Ask me to pass the soy sauce.
Oh, does that come up much
on the Space Station?
Mostly with Asian
and Jewish astronauts.
-All right, pass the soy sauce.
-Coming up.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[KEYBOARD CLICKING]
[KEYBOARD CONTINUES CLICKING]
-So how's work?
-Oh, It's not bad.
-Kind of hungry.
-Yeah, we all are.
Just wait.
You realize, Penny, that the technology
that went into this arm...
...will one day make unskilled
food servers such as yourself obsolete.
Really? They're gonna make a robot
that spits on your hamburger?
I thought you broke up with her.
Why is she here?
Okay, here we go.
Passing the soy sauce.
Put out your hand.
[PENNY CHUCKLES]
-That's amazing.
-I wouldn't say "amazing."
At best, it's a modest leap forward...
...from the basic technology
that gave us Country Bear Jamboree.
-Hey, Sheldon? Ahem.
-Yes?
-Peace?
-No, not peace. Hang on.
Does NASA know you're using that thing
as a napkin holder?
Are you kidding? They still think
it's in a secure locker at JPL.
-You stole it?
-Borrowed.
The trick is to carry it out to your car
like you own it.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Excuse me.
Oh, Amy's at the dry-cleaner's
and she's made a very amusing pun.
Ahem. "I don't care for perchloroethylene
and I don't like glycol ether."
Get it? She doesn't like glycol ether.
Sounds like "either."
[GIGGLES]
"L_O_L."
Who's Amy?
-His girlfriend.
-Sheldon has a girlfriend?
-She's not my girlfriend.
-How long?
-Four months.
-She's not my girlfriend.
For four months
I have been asking you what's new.
You never thought to go with
"Sheldon has a girlfriend"?
-She's not my girlfriend.
-Teh, teh, teh.
-How did they meet?
-Raj and I entered Sheldon's information...
...on a dating site
and it spit out Amy Farrah Fowler.
Oh, my God! Sheldon and Amy.
Or as we call them, "Shamy."
[PENNY SQUEALS]
Shamy. I am so digging the Shamy.
All right. Everyone, pay attention.
Yes, I have a friend named
Amy Farrah Fowler.
Yes, she is female.
Yes, we communicate on a daily basis,
but no, she is not my girlfriend.
Okay, well,
what do you communicate about?
Well, my work in physics,
her work in neurobiology...
...and most recently, the possibility
of our having a child together.
Thank you.
Wait a minute, a child?
You never see this girl.
You just e-mail and text and Twitter...
...and now you're considering
having a baby?
Amy pointed out
that between the two of us...
...our genetic material
has the potential of producing the first...
...In a line of intellectually superior
benign overlords...
...to guide humanity
to a brighter tomorrow.
I'm guessing that future historians
will condemn us...
...for not taking this opportunity
to kill Sheldon.
-Okay. I have a question.
-Yes, Penny.
You don't even like people touching you.
How are you gonna have sex?
Why on earth would we have sex?
Oh, honey, did your mom
not have the talk with you?
You know, when your private parts
started growing?
I'm quite aware of the way
humans usually reproduce...
...which is messy, unsanitary...
...and based on living next to you
for three years...
...Involves loud and unnecessary appeals
to a deity.
-Oh, God.
-Yes, exactly.
Consequently, if Amy and I choose
to bring new life into this world...
...It will be accomplished clinically...
...with fertility experts in a lab
with Petri dishes.
Which reminds me, you have broad hips
and a certain corn-fed vigor.
Is your womb available for rental?
Still digging the Shamy?
Look, Sheldon, before you race off
to the fertility clinic...
...you might wanna think about...
...gee, I don't know, maybe actually
spending some time with her.
-You mean dating?
-Yeah.
-I can't date Amy.
-Why not?
She's not my girlfriend.
Don't think of it as dating a girlfriend.
Think of it as, uh, getting to know
the future mother of your child.
Oh.
I hadn't considered that.
I suppose she will have to have
access to our progeny.
And you don't think I can achieve
the required intimacy via text messaging?
-Probably not.
-Hmm.
It would appear as if the phone
companies have been lying to me.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
You do realize
I stand on the other side of the door...
...waiting for you
to finish knocking three times.
I know. I can see the shadow
of your feet under the door.
Yeah. My point is it's a waste of time.
If you're looking for an example
of a waste of time. ..
...I would refer you to the conversation
we're having right now.
-What do you want?
-I've decided to take your advice...
...and have arranged to go on a date
with Amy Farrah Fowler.
-Oh, that's great. Have fun.
“Wait. You have to drive me.
-What?
-You know I don't drive.
-Well, go ask Leonard.
- I did.
He said, and I quote, "Ask Penny.
It was her cockamamie idea."
Leonard said "cockamamie"?
Actually, I'm paraphrasing. Having
been raised in a Christian household. ..
...I'm uncomfortable
with the language he used.
And to be honest, I'm not
entirely comfortable with "cockamamie.”
Okay, fine. When's the date?
-Now.
-Now?
Hurry, we're going to be late.
Sheldon, did it ever occur to you
that I might have other plans?
I'm sorry. Do you have other plans?
Well, no, not per se, but....
And so this conversation is as pointless
as your door-knocking soliloquy?
Let me get my cockamamie keys.
HOWARD:
Oh, God, that feels so good.
[I MOANING]
Yeah, that's the spot. Oh, baby.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, dinner's ready!
I'll eat later, I'm busy!
Oh, yeah. Just like a real hand.
Hmm.
-Thank you for driving me.
You're welcome.
I wish you weren't wearing flip-flops.
Dangerous to drive in flip-flops.
-Sheldon.
-Sorry.
I just don't wanna be
yet another flip-flop fatality.
Can I ask you a question?
Given your
community-college education...
...I encourage you to ask me
as many as possible.
Yeah, ahem, well, my question is,
and I'm pretty sure I know the answer...
...is this your first date?
That depends.
Does square dancing with my sister...
...at a Teens for Jesus
Fourth of July hoedown count as a date?
-No.
-Then this is my first date.
Okay, well, then there's a couple of things
you should probably know.
I have a master's degree
and two doctorates.
The things I should know, I do know.
My point is,
I know more about dating than you...
...and if you were as smart as you think
you are, you would listen to me.
If you know so much,
how come I have a date tonight...
...and you have nothing better to do
than drive me to it?
Fair point.
You know, there's something I've
always wondered about Aquaman.
-Yeah?
-Where does he poop?
-What?
“What would a toilet look like in Atlantis?
How would you flush it?
And when you did flush it...
...where would the poop go?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hold that thought.
Hey, Howard, what's going on?
Wha--? Hold on. Howard.
Howard, slow down.
The robot hand
is stuck on your what?
You're not gonna believe this.
[PENNY CLEARS THROAT]
So, um, Amy, Sheldon tells me
you're a neuro-something-or-other.
Neurobiologist.
Your "check engine” light is on.
Yeah, it's okay.
-But the light indicates--
-Don't bother.
I've wasted many an hour
tilting at that particular windmill.
What is that scent you're wearing?
It smells great.
Dandruff shampoo.
I have dry scalp.
Ah, well, your hair looks very nice.
Are you a homosexual?
-No, I was just giving you a compliment.
-Hmm.
I would have been more flattered
if you were a homosexual.
-Guys, how about some music?
-Oh, I wouldn't care for that.
-Amy?
-No, thank you.
Okay. Uncomfortable silence it is.
Hey, Sheldon, have you told Amy...
...what it was like for you
growing up in Texas?
No.
Well, why don't you tell her?
All right.
It was hell.
Any follow-up, Amy?
No.
I, myself, grew up in Nebraska.
Small town outside of Omaha.
Yeah, nice place, mostly family farms,
a few meth labs.
I'm sorry, how is this better
than uncomfortable silence?
I don't know.
I was just trying something.
Muggles.
You slipped and fell into a robot hand?
Yes.
Penis first.
Yes. Now, help me!
I'd suggest a lubricant...
...but I have a feeling
you fell on some of that as well.
Not funny, Leonard.
Really? A robot hand's
got a death grip on your junk, dude.
That's funny, ask anyone.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Please, before my mother walks in,
get this off me.
Okay, let's see.
No. Don't touch.
The program is paused.
-Then let's unpause it.
- I loaded the wrong program.
The hand thinks
it's holding a screwdriver.
If you continue the program,
it's gonna start twisting.
All-- All-- All right, how about this?
When Winnie the Pooh
got his head stuck in the honey tree...
...his friends all grabbed onto him
and pulled and pulled.
You do what you want. I'm not touching
another man's honey tree.
All right, uh, forget pulling.
How about we get an electric saw
and cut it off?
What? No saws!
One circumcision was enough.
How about an acetylene torch?
I can't believe
this needs to be said out loud.
-No pulling, no saws, no torches.
-Then what do you want us to do?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, I made cookies for you...
...and your little friends!
That's great, Mom, thanks!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I'll bring them up with Hawaiian Punch!
-Don't come up here!
MRS WOLOWITZ: Why not?
Are you ashamed of your mother?
Yes, but that's not the point!
Get me out of here.
You have any ideas, Raj?
Right now, all I can think about
is cookies and Hawaiian Punch.
Hey, here's another possible topic
of conversation.
This is a big night for Sheldon.
-Right, Sheldon?
-Big night?
The winter solstice is a big night.
It's over 14 hours
in Southern California.
-That's an amusing factoid.
-Thank you.
No, no. My point is, uh,
tonight is Sheldon's first official date.
Discuss.
-Is this true?
-Apparently a semi-incestuous...
...Teens for Jesus
Fourth of July hoedown didn't count.
So, um, Amy, what about you?
Do you date much?
Once a year.
It's a deal I made with my mother...
...In exchange for her silence
on the matter...
...and the use of her George Foreman Grill
that seals in the flavor without the fat.
What about you?
Do you go on many dates”?
Uh, yeah, I wouldn't say many. A few.
[GIGGLES]
What's ... 7?
[IMITATES SHELDON'S GIGGLE]
Your characterization of approximately
171 different men as a few.
What--7
Where did you get 171 men?
Simple extrapolation.
In the three years that |I've known you,
you were single for two.
During that time,
I saw 17 different suitors.
If we work backwards. ..
...correcting for observation bias
and postulate an initial dating age of 15--
Whoa, wait, wait, wait.
I did not start dating at 15.
-I'm sorry. Sixteen?
-Fourteen.
My mistake.
Now assuming the left side of a bell curve
peaking around the present...
...that would bring the total
up to 193 men, plus or minus eight men.
Remarkable. Did you have
sexual intercourse with all of these men?
-No.
SHELDON: No.
Although that number
would be fairly easy to calculate.
Based on the number
of awkward encounters I've had. ..
...with strange men
leaving her apartment...
...plus the number of times
she's returned home. ..
...wearing same clothes
she wore the night before--
-I think you've made your point.
-So we multiply a 193...
...minus 21 men
before the loss of virginity...
...80 172 times 0.18
gives us 30.96 sexual partners.
Let's round that up to 31.
Okay, Sheldon. You are so wrong.
That is not even close
to the real number.
I'm gonna need a drink over here.
This is very interesting.
Cultural perceptions are subjective.
Penny, to your mind, are you a slut?
No. No.
No.
Let's just all finish our dinners,
okay?
This Is an interesting topic.
How many sexual encounters
have you had?
Does volunteering for an experiment
in which orgasm was achieved...
...by electronically stimulating
the pleasure centers of the brain count?
I should think so.
Then 128.
Okay, come on.
Almost there.
Don't tug. No tugging.
Next time take your own advice.
Excuse me. Could you help us out?
My, my, my.
What do we have here?
- I slipped and fell.
-Yeah, we get that a lot.
-What is this?
-It's a robot arm.
Where's the rest of the robot?
I only built the arm.
Because that's all you needed, right?
Can you please just help me?
All right. All right.
Hang on, stay calm.
[ON PA]
I need an orderly with a wheelchair.
I've got a robot hand
grasping a man's penis out here.
You think you could be
a little more discreet?
I'm sorry, we don't have a code
for robot hand grasping a man's penis.
Why is it hooked up to a computer?
-It's what controls the arm.
-But it's frozen.
Did you try turning it off
and back on again?
No, you see,
it's more complicated than that--
No, wait!
Winnie the Pooh
is out of the honey tree.
Now can we have cookies
and Hawaiian Punch?
You were right.
This was a very productive evening.
I saw a whole new side
of Amy Farrah Fowler tonight.
PENNY:
I did not have sex with 31 guys.
SHELDON: I'll be happy to check the math,
but numbers don't lie, Penny.
In any event, now that Amy and I
have spent quality time together...
...| feel much more confident proceeding
to the next stage of our relationship.
And that is?
Using in vitro fertilization
and a surrogate uterus...
...to gift humanity with our progeny.
You're still on that?
In these uncertain times,
doesn't humanity deserve a gift?
Okay, you know what? I'm gonna
come at this in a whole new way.
Sheldon, if you try to make a baby
with Amy in a Petri dish...
...I'm gonna tell your mother on you.
Well, that's no threat.
My mother's
always wanted a grandchild.
Really? Your deeply religious,
born-again Christian mother...
...wants a test-tube grandbaby
born out of wedlock?
curses.
If I'd thought of that in the first place,
I could've saved myself this whole night.
Well, it's not that late. You could
still go out and look for number 32.
Good night.
Hey, Howard. What's up?
-I've decided not to procreate.
-Yeah, yeah, great.
Howard, uh, slow down.
What do you mean, "It happened again"?
[English - US - SDH]